Miscellaneous periodical contributions, 1921-1957 PS3519 .A39
Lilly Library
- Miscellaneous material by Margaret Weymouth Jackson, 1921-1957
  - An Ill Wind. Excerpt from The Star Weekly, 21 January 1950; p. 6. (Box 16)
  - If the Shoe Fits. Excerpt from The Star Weekly, 20 December 1952; p. 5. (Box 16)
  - The Hero. In Great Sports Stories, ed. Herman L. Masin, New York, Berkley Publishing Corp., circa 1957; p. 18-36. (Box 16)